One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Necessary Evil
شرٌ لا بدّ منه
This is my Star Shield.
هذه درع النجمة
What's up with this guy's body?
ما خطب جسده؟
He's no longer human!
!لا يُعدّ بشريًّا
Flames again?!
!لهيب ثانيةً؟
Master Nail!
سيّد المسامير
Moon Walk!
مشية القمر
He keeps jumping outta the way! We're getting nowhere like this!
!طار ثانية !لن نحلّ شيئًا هكذا
Looks like my four powers aren't much use here.
ما باليد حيلة إن كانت قواي الأربع لا تجدي نفعًا
Apologies, but since I haven't mastered finger pistol yet,
آسف، سأستخدم بعض الدعائم !بما أنّي لم أتقن مسدّس الإصبع بعد
Alright! This is my chance to go to the next car!
!سأذهب إلى المقطورة التالية بينما تسنح لي الفرصة الآن
Hey, hold it, you bastard!
!تمهّل أيّها الوغد
Can't take your eyes off him!
!لا أستطيع التهاون معه
He fell for it.
انطلت عليه
Beans Left!
فاصوليا اليسرى
Too bad...
...مع الأسف
I figured...
...توقعت
you'd do something like that!
!أنّك ستفعل شيئًا كهذا
Ow...!
!مؤلم
Gotcha!
!تأثّر بها
You son of a bitch...
...أيّها الوغد
Ouchie Finger!
الإصبع المؤلم
Shave!
الركض الفائق
Dammit...
سحقًا
He's figured me out...
لاحظ إذًا
Tempest Kick!
ركلة العاصفة
That one grazed me!
!خدشتني
He sure moves around a lot!
!إنّه يتحرّك كثيرًا
So your weak point...
...نقطة ضعفك
is your back, huh?
هي ظهرك إذًا؟
And I can see through your cheap tricks.
وفهمتُ حيلك التافهة أيضًا
It's only a matter of time before I win, isn't it?
فوزي مسألة وقت الآن، أليس كذلك؟
Don't get cocky!
!لا تغترّ بنفسك
I have no weak point if I do this.
لا أملك نقطة ضعف إن فعلت هذا
Franky...
فرانكي
Invincible!
المنيع
Invincible
منيع
Give up yet, you stupid weasel?
!هل استسلمت أيّها السرعوب اللعين؟
How do you even respond to that...?
لا أدري ما أقوله له
But really, dude, you've got some terrible luck.
يا إلهي يا لك من منحوس
You've gone and pissed me off…
أغضبتني
and I happen to be especially super this week.
وصادف أنّي خارق هذا الأسبوع
Say, buddy...
،أخبرني يا أخ
You ever heard of a centaur?
أتعرف الوحش المسمى قنطور؟
The horse monster that's human from the waist up?
صاحب الهيئة البشرية من فوق وسطه وهيئة حصان أدناه، أليس كذلك؟
What about it?
ما خطبه؟
Con... vert!
!تحوّل
Convert
تحوّل
Pervert
منحرف
Don't tell me he's gonna...
...لا يمكن
Franky...
فرانكي
Centaur!
القنطور
That's backwards! Your body goes in front!
!إنّه العكس !يفترض أن يكون جسدك في المقدمة
Don't knock it till you've seen its horsepower.
!أجّل هذا التذمّر إلى أن ترى قوته الهجوميّة
Dammit! You've got some nerve!
!سحقًا! يا لغطرستك !إنّك مجرّد مجرم
My noodle fists are gone!
!اختفت قبضات المعكرونة خاصتي
Am I...
هل أنا
an onion or something?!
!بصلة؟
It's pointless to keep fighting.
لا فائدة من الاستمرار بالقتال
Accept your loss and let me pass.
اقبل بخسارتك ودعني أمر
Accept my loss? Why would I?! Who says I'm losing?!
!أقبل بخسارتي؟ مستحيل !لم أخسر
I'm Wanze, the ace of CP7!
!أنا وانزي، نجم السّي بي 7
Unfortunately for you, I understand the importance of this mission.
مع الأسف، فإنّي أفهم أهميّة هذه المهمة
The government has been pursuing your crewmate, Nico Robin, for a long time.
،نيكو روبين، واحدة من رفاقكم هي امرأة كانت تلاحقها الحكومة لسنوات عديدة
You're a moron if you think I'd just let you take her!
!كيف لي أن أسلّمها بسهولة أيّها الأحمق؟
Ramen Kenpo: Noodle Nail Knocker!
فن القتال بالرامن: عصا المعكرونة القارعة
When preparing an onion, you must first cut off the stem and root without bruising the flesh.
عليك أن تقطع ساق وجذر البصل دون أن تؤذيها من الداخل
If you slice the fiber in one go...
،إن قطعت الألياف دفعة واحدة
the cut results in a pristine, glossy surface.
فإنّ السطح المقطوع سيبدو جميلًا ويحافظ على بريقه
Stop it! Stay back!
!توقف! تراجع
Ramen Beam!
شعاع الرامن
Épluchage!
التقشير
Y-You cut me!
!قـ-قُطعت
Oh? I didn't get cut.
!ماذا؟ لم أُقطع
And if you don't put love into the smallest of tasks, like peeling skins,
علاوة على ذلك، إن لم تمتلك ما يكفي ،من الحب لشيء صغير كتقشير الجلد
it'll spoil the taste of any dish.
فسيكون مذاق طبقك سيئًا مهما كان
Kitchen knives aren't swords. They're not for cutting people.
،سكاكين المطبخ ليست سيوفًا لذا فإنّي لا أقطع الناس بها
But in case you hadn't noticed, your armor is–
ولكن عليك إدراك أنّك فقدت درعك
Kitchen Knife Throw!
رمية سكاكين المطبخ
You son of a...
...أيّها
Œil!
ركلة العين
M-My eyes are caving in!
!عـ-عيناي دُعستا إلى الداخل
Let them.
دعهما تدعسان
Now, shut up and surrender.
هيّا، اصمت واستسلم
You numbskull! Why would I?!
!أيّها الغبي! مستحيل
I don't get why the heck you would want to rescue a woman like that!
لا أفهم سبب رغبتكم !بإنقاذ تلك المرأة من الأساس
You guys don't actually know Nico Robin's true nature, do you?!
لا بدّ أنّكم لا تعرفون طبيعة نيكو روبين الحقيقيّة، أليس كذلك؟
That woman is...
تلك المرأة
Nez!
ركلة الأنف
Joue!
الخد
Bouche!
الفم
Dents!
الأسنان
Menton!
الذقن
If you keep talking, I'm gonna rearrange your face.
إن قلت شيئًا أكثر، فسأغير شكل جسدك
H-H-Hold on a sec!
!تـ-تـ-تمهّل
I-I feel like my face shrank! Stop it!
!أ-أشعر أنّ وجهي صغر! توقّف
I-If you don't know about her, I'll tell you.
إ-إن كنت لا تعرف، فسأخبرك
Everyone knows!
!الجميع يعرفون
She's a depraved devil!
!إنّها شيطان فاسد
Parage... Shot!
ركلات التشذيب
D-D-Dammit!
!سـ-سـ-سحقًا
My face caved in! Mirror! I need a mirror!
!دعس وجهي !مرآة! مرآة
Y-Y-You bastard!
!أ-أ-أيّها الوغد
H-How dare you dent my precious eyes and nose?!
!كـ-كيف تجرؤ على بعج عيناي وأنفي اللذين أفخر بهم؟
You're a demon!
!إنّك شيطان
Oh, hey, they're back to normal.
عادتا كما كانتا
Y-You're right!
!إ-إنّك محق
I felt like they went back a little just now.
أشعر أنّهما عادتا قليلًا للتو
G-Guess I just imagined it.
كـ-كان ذلك مجرد خيال
You're guilty of three sins.
ارتكبت ثلاث خطايا
First, you claimed to be a cook in front of me.
الأولى، ادّعيت أنّك طبّاخ أمامي
Second, you treated food with disrespect.
الثّانية، لم تحترم الطعام
Third...
الثّالثة، أسأت لرفيقتنا
You're the very definition of "all bark, no bite."
إنّك لا تجيد إلّا الكلام
Hey, centaur! Those four legs don't appear to be helping much!
أيّها القنطور، لا أدري ما الذي قوى فيك ،بعد أن أصبحت تمتلك أربع أرجل
I-I-I'm gonna fall!
!سـ-سـ-سأقع
What a sorry sight.
تبدو مثيرًا للشفقة
Dammit!
!سحقًا
Need a hand?
هل تريدني أن أنقذك؟
You weasel!
!أيّها الوغد
Not quite...!
!ليس بعد
You wanna give me a hand?!
!أتقول أنّك ستساعدني؟
I'm doing just fine, jackass!
!لا أحتاج ذلك أيّها الغبي
I've finally got you.
أمسكت بك أخيرًا
Now tell me if you still think my being four-legged was pointless!
فلتعرف الآن ما إن كانت أرجلي !الأربع ذات فائدة أم لا
Shut up, you jerk!
!اصمت أيّها الوغد
Give me my signature features back!
!أعد لي خصائصي
My friend is waiting to be rescued on the other side of that door you're blocking.
تنتظر رفيقتي إنقاذنا لها في الجانب الآخر من الباب الموجود خلفك
When I say I won't let you go through, I mean it!
!عندما أقول أنّي لن أسمح لك بالعبور، فأعني ذلك
Backstreet Ramen Kenpo: Poison Noodle Cleaver!
فن القتال بالرامن: التقنية السريّة سكّين المطبخ القاطعة للمعكرونة السامّة
Touch this, and you're dead!
!ستموت إن لمستها
Now, now, now, now!
!هيّا، هيّا، هيّا، هيّا
Aren't you guys being deceived by that woman, too?!
أليست تلك المرأة تخدعكم جميعًا أيضًا؟
She's the lowest of the low,
إنّها امرأة سافلة عاشت ،على خيانة تلو الأخرى
a serial backstabber who's survived up until now by hiding in the shadows!
!ونجت حتّى الآن بالاختباء في الظلال
It's the end of the line for you!
!سأسلب حياتك
Take this!
!خذ هذه
Three-Point...
نحت
Découpage!
الثلاث نقاط
He's got me completely pinned down!
!أمسك بكلتا يديّ ورجلي
I got careless!
!أرخيت دفاعي
Careless?
أرخيت دفاعك؟
Excuses, excuses.
لا أريد الأعذار
Actually, why don't you take this opportunity to say some final words, buddy?
لمَ لا تستغل هذه الفرصة لتقول كلماتك الأخيرة، يا أخ؟
You're not thinking you're gonna keep fighting after this, are you?
أتعتقد أنّ القتال سيستمر؟
What?!
!ماذا؟
Well, I guess it makes sense when you've been dodging all my attacks.
هذا طبيعي لأنّك تفاديت كلّ هجماتي حتّى الآن
You don't know how killer my punches really are.
بما أنّك لا تعرف مدى فتك ضربتي
Ultimate...
المطرقة القصوى
Hey, where the hell did you come from?
أنت، من أين أتيت؟
Did you finish off that ramen guy?
هل اعتنيت بأمر صاحب الرامن؟
Yep, just now.
فعلتُ توًّا
It's getting noisy around here.
أصبحت الأمور صاخبة فجأة
So the soldiers for this escort mission were annihilated after all?
جنود مهمّة الحراسة هذه أُبيدوا بنهاية المطاف إذًا؟
They were never anything to write home about.
لم نتوقع منهم شيئًا أصلًا
They're the ones who kidnapped Robin, right?
هؤلاء هم من اختطفوا روبين-تشان، أليس كذلك؟
Be careful. They use strange martial arts.
توخّ الحذر، إنّهم يستخدمون فنونًا قتالية غريبة
Who is this?
من هذا؟
He must be that CP9 greenhorn that Corgi was prattling on about.
لا بدّ أنّه عضو السّي بي 9 الجديد الذي تحدث عنه كورغي
If I recall correctly, he's a four power master named Nero or something.
إلّم تخنّي الذاكرة، فإنّه مستخدم للقوى الأربع ويدعى نيرو على ما أظن
Dammit!
!سحقًا
You're gonna get it now!
!لن أغفر لك الآن
People call me a fighting prodigy!
!يدعونني عبقري القتال
I don't care anymore...
لم يعد يهمني هذا
You're dead meat!
!سأقتلك
Hey, "greenhorn."
أيّها الجديد
You... You must be Rob Lucci, right?
أ-أنت روب لوتشي، أليس كذلك؟
Sorry for the late introduction...
آسف لأنّي لم أقدّم نفسي باكرًا
One moment, please.
انتظر قليلًا من فضلك
I just gotta kill this guy, and then...
...سأقتله الآن ومن ثم
Our orders are to capture Franky alive.
سنقبض على فرانكي حيًّا
To put your personal feelings before a mission is...
سمحتَ لمشاعرك بالسيطرة عليك ونسيتَ مهمتنا
No, forget it.
لا، انسَ الأمر
You've got three seconds. Start running.
سأمنحك ثلاث ثوانٍ، لذا اهرب بسرعة
Three...
...ثلاثة
Run...?! From who?!
أهرب؟ ممّن؟
Two...
اثنان
Huh?! Wait a second!
!ماذا؟ لحظة
You're kidding, right?!
أنت تمزح، أليس كذلك؟
One.
واحد
Stop! You're making a mistake!
!توقّف! لا تتحامق
Shave!
الركض الفائق
A person like you who does everything half-assed...
شخص مثلك لا ينجز الأمر على أكمل وجه
is unfit for CP9!
!ليس مؤهلًا ليكون في السّي بي 9
Unless you've mastered all six powers, you aren't superhuman, boy.
لستَ إنسانًا خارقًا ما لم تتقن الأساليب الستة كلها أيّها الصبي
Kalifa.
كاليفا
Yes.
نعم
Inform the chief later...
أعلمي رئيسنا لاحقًا
that the newbie was too weak to be of any use.
أنّ الجديد كان ضعيفًا جدًّا لدرجة أنّ لا فائدة ترجى منه
Roger.
مفهوم
These guys stand for justice?
أيفترض أنّ هؤلاء يعملون من أجل العدالة؟
Can't tell which side is evil, huh?
لا أدري من هو الشرير
I guess I don't have to ask why you're here, intruder.
،لعلي لستُ بحاجة إلى سؤالك عن غاية تواجدك أيّها الدخيل
Given the way you opened that door, you don't seem to have much patience.
،وفق طريقتك بفتح الباب فلا يبدو أنّك تملك كثيرًا من الصبر
Yeah, guess I wasn't raised right.
نعم، لم أُربَّ جيّدًا
If this is about Nico Robin...
إن كان هذا يتعلق بنيكو روبين
give it up.
فاستسلموا
You're sticking your noses into matters beyond you.
إنّها مسألة أكبر من أن تقحموا أنفسكم فيها
There are people in the world who are born under unlucky stars...
ثمّة أشخاص في هذا العالم ولدوا تحت نجم منحوس
People who are better off dead for everyone's sake.
أشخاص من الأفضل أن يموتوا لمصلحة الجميع
For example...
...على سبيل المثال
Suppose a devil exists that could destroy the world.
افترض وجود شيطان قد يحرق العالم على بكرة أبيه
If the one with the power to awaken that devil is an innocent, eight-year-old girl,
إن كان الشخص القادر على إيقاظه هي طفلة بريئة لا تتعدى الثمانية أعوام
don't you think...
...أفلا تعتقد
that someone should kill that girl for everyone's sake?
أنّ أحدًا ما عليه قتل تلك الفتاة من أجل مصلحة الجميع؟
Huh? What are you getting at?
ما الذي ترمي إليه؟
I'm explaining Nico Robin's situation to you.
إنني أبيّن لك حقيقة نيكو روبين
These days, she's a fully-fledged criminal...
،إنّها مجرمة حقيقيّة الآن
but that was how it all started.
ولكن كانت البداية بتلك البساطة
For as long as she can remember, her very existence has been a sin.
وجودها بحد ذاته ذنبًا منذ نعومة أظافرها
She can only make people happy by disappearing.
لا يمكنها أن تسعد الآخرين إلّا إن اختفت
That is the misfortune she carries.
هذا هو سوء الطالع الذي تحمله
Essentially, she should've died 20 years ago.
أساسًا، كان من المفترض أن تموت قبل 20 سنة
I'm truly glad that this woman...
أنا مسرورٌ حقًا أنّ هذه المرأة ستموت
Hey...
...أنت
That's enough outta you!
!كفاك ثرثرة
You son of a bitch!
!أيّها الوغد
Don't you dare say another word!
!لا تفتح فمك أكثر من هذا
That being said, the government will probably spend many years...
ولكن، ستقضي الحكومة سنين عديدة
wringing out every drop of Nico Robin's knowledge, experience, and intelligence.
،باستخلاص كلّ معرفة نيكو روبين خبراتها وذكائها
I can't even imagine the agony she'll endure from now until her demise... Just think about–
كم ستعاني تلك المرأة قبل أن تموت ...راقب ذلك جيّدًا و
No way in hell we'll let that happen!
!لن أسمح بحدوث ذلك
Hey, hey, wait, Robin!
!لحظة، لحظة، تمهلي يا روبين
You shouldn't go that way!
!لا ينبغي لك أن تذهبي إلى هناك
Hey! Seriously! Seriously! Wait!
!أنت! أنا جاد! أنا جاد
Hey, I said, wait!
!أخبرتك أن تتمهلي
Robin!
!روبين-تشان
O-Oh crap...
هـ-هذا سيّئ
Thank goodness! Are you okay?! Are you hurt?!
!أنا مسرور! هل أنتِ بخير؟ !هل تأذيتِ؟
This is really bad!
!يا للمصيبة
It was one thing getting in from the outside, but then taking out that official...!
،بعد أن تكبدت عناء الدخول من الخارج !وهزمت ذلك الجندي
So that's Nico Robin?
هذه نيكو روبين إذًا؟
She does kinda look like that photo on the wanted poster.
إنّها تشبه تلك التي في ملصق المطلوبين بالفعل
Let's go back together this time!
!لنرجع إلى الجميع هذه المرة
I'll knock these guys out in no time flat... Alright, Robin?!
،سأهزم هؤلاء فورًا !حسنًا يا روبين-تشان؟
Usopp!
!أوسوب
What're you doing, Robin?!
!ماذا تفعلين يا روبين-تشان؟
Ow...
...مؤلم
Even if I explain,
،حتّى وإن شرحت لكم فلن تفهموا، أليس كذلك؟
Sir Franky!
!فرانكي-كن
Detach car three!
!افصل المقطورة الثالثة
What're we gonna do?!
!ماذا سنفعل؟
Run!
!سنهرب
Run?!
!نهرب؟
Hey, what do you mean?!
!لحظة، ماذا تعني؟
You, too, make haste! One moment will decide the game!
!أنت! أسرع أيضًا !ستنتهي المواجهة في لحظة
Don't let Franky slip away.
لا تسمح لفرانكي بالهروب
Roger.
مفهوم
Sogeking...
سوغيكنغ
Smoke Star!
نجم الدخان
What a low-down humbug...!
!يا للسخافة
We got Nico Robin!
!أخذنا نيكو روبين
Hey! Put me down!
!اتركني
– Alright!
!حسنًا
Run!
!اهربا
Go baaaack!
!ارجعوا
Why?! We came all this way!
!لماذا؟! بعد أن قطعنا كلّ هذا الطريق
Mr. Straw Hat!
!قبعة القش
– That's right! Tell us why!
!صحيح! أخبرنا عن السبب
Not you guys!
!ليس كذلك
– Huh?
ماذا؟
That stupid frog jumped on the railway tracks! Go back, froggy! Get away from the train!
كنت أقول لذلك الضفدع الذي قفز على !السكّة أن يرجع
It's Yokozuna!
!إنّه يوكوزونا
Him?
إنّه هناك؟
– What's up with that huge frog?!
!ما هذا الضفدع العملاق؟
Watch out!
!احترس
Get outta the way, frog!
!ابتعد أيّها الضفدع
We're gonna crash!
!سنصطدم
Alright!
!مرحى
We got Robin back!
!أعدنا روبين
Well, that sure surprised me.
ولكن هذا فاجأني حقًا
To think we switched to a strategic retreat...
لم أتوقع أن نبدّل استراتيجيتنا إلى استراتيجية الهروب فجأة
No one would expect something as dumb as a smoke screen.
القنبلة الدخانية سخيفة جدًّا لدرجة أنّ لا أحد يفكّر باستخدامها عادة
It's best if we can achieve our goal without fighting scary guys like them.
سيكون من الأفضل لو تمكنّا من تحقيق هدفنا دون قتال أشخاص مرعبين مثلهم
But...
...ولكن
I don't know if things are gonna be that simple.
لا أدري ما إن كانت الأمور ستسير بهذه البساطة
Yeah. Don't let your guard down until the cars are really far apart.
أجل، لا ترخوا دفاعاتكم إلى أن تبتعد المقطورات تمامًا
What the hell...?!
!ما هذا؟
Thorny whips?!
!أسواط شائكة؟
I caught it...
أمسكت بها
Blueno.
بلونو
Right.
أجل
Is he gonna cross using the whips?!
!أسيستخدمها للعبور؟
They pulled us back!
!سحبونا
That power's insane!
!يا لها من قوّة
A smoke screen? What a pointless trick...
قنبلة دخانيّة؟ يا لها من حيلة سخيفة
I guess it was too good to be true.
لم تجدِ نفعًا بالفعل إذًا
The Straw Hat Pirates are to be left alive.
لا تقتلوا أيًّا من طاقم قبعة القش
That was the agreement.
هذا ما وعدناها به
Sogeking!
!سوغيكينغ
Oh, yes?
نعم؟
Protect Robin! Got it?!
احم روبين-تشان مهما كلّف الأمر
Huh...? Yeah!
!ماذا؟ نعم
Sorry, but I'm going to...
...آسف، ولكن
make you let go!
!سأجبرك على إفلاتها
Why is his body so hard?
ما هذه الصلابة؟
Didn't I tell you they use weird martial arts?!
ألم أخبرك أنّهم يستخدمون !فنونًا قتالية غريبة؟
Concassé!
سحق
That boy's kicks are no joke.
يا لها من ركلة ثقيلة
He almost broke through iron body.
كاد الجسد الحديديّ أن يتحطّم
Blueno, don't take him lightly.
لا تستخف به يا بلونو
He may not have a bounty, but he's one of their heavy hitters.
،لا توجد مكافأة على رأسه ولكنّه أحد قواهم الرئيسيّة
Whoa, R-Robin! H-Hey, h-hold on a sec!
!ر-روبين! تمهلي
Ow... Wh-What're you doing?
مؤلم مـ-ماذا تفعلين؟
Ocho Fleurs!
ثمان أزهار
Clutch!
تشبّث
Long Nose!
!طويل الأنف
Hey! What are you doing, Robin?!
!لماذا يا روبين-تشان؟
How many times do I have to tell you?! Leave me alone!
!كم مرّة تريدونني أن أكرّر كلامي؟ !اتركوني وحدي
No way...
...لا يمكن
Hey, stay on your toes.
أنت، انتبه
Eyebrows!
!ذو الحواجب
For the love of... Why are you all being so stubborn?!
يا إلهي، لماذا جميعكم عنيدون
You're supposed to be friends, aren't you?!
!حتّى مع أصدقائكم؟
This is...
...أليست هذه
the perfect chance to get away, right?!
!فرصة مثاليّة للهروب؟
Franky!
!فرانكي
That was uncalled for.
لم يكن لذلك داعٍ
Didn't expect that, did you?
لم تتوقعوا هذا، أليس كذلك؟
Why are you siding with them in the first place?
لماذا أنت إلى جانبهم أساسًا؟
I can't stand watching them act like that.
لا أتحمل رؤية فريق لا يستطيع العودة !إلى بعضه رغم أنّه يريد ذلك
I wonder who you're talking about.
أتساءل عمّن تتحدّث
You guys, don't worry about me!
!أنتم، لا تقلقوا بشأني
I've got a plan!
!لديّ خطّة
Once you've joined up with Straw Hat, get back to town somehow!
،عندما تلتقون بقبعة القش !عودوا إلى المدينة بطريقة ما
Franky!
!فرانكي
Wait!
!انتظروا
I won't run away!
!لن أهرب
Wait, Robin.
انتظري يا روبين-تشان
Why are you still acting like this?
لماذا تتصرفين هكذا بعد كلّ هذا؟
We came to rescue you knowing the full story!
!أتينا لإنقاذك بعلمنا لكلّ الظروف
If we can just do something about the government's buster call,
،إن فعلنا شيئًا بخصوص هجوم الحكومة، نداء الدّمار
then you wouldn't have a reason to listen to them, right?!
!فيفترض ألّا يوجد سبب لأن تطيعيهم، أليس كذلك؟
That buster call...
...نداء الدّمار
is precisely the problem.
المشكلة بحد ذاتها
Tempest Kick!
ركلة العاصفة
Wha...?!
...مـ
Sanji!
!سانجي
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
He came outta nowhere!
!ظهر من العدم
Blueno disappeared?!
!اختفى بلونو؟
He didn't disappear.
لم يختف
He used "Air Door"—the power that makes his Door-Door Fruit actually worth something—
،"استخدم قدرة "باب الهواء القدرة الأهم لفاكهة الباب
to create a door in the air itself.
لم يقم إلّا بخلق باب من حائط الهواء
You can't escape from us...
لا تستطيعون الهروب منّا
It's simply not possible.
أبدًا
Let Robin...
...اترك روبين
go–
!تذهب
Finger Pistol.
مسدّس الإصبع
Usopp!
!أوسوب
Iron Body.
الجسد الحديديّ
Are you feeling that attack from earlier?
أأثرت هجمتي السابقة عليك؟
That kick was laughable.
يا لها من ركلة ضعيفة
How stubborn.
يا لك من عنيد
Stop it!
!توقّف
I won't run away.
لن أهرب
That should be enough.
يفترض أنّ هذا كافٍ
They're the ones who keep attacking me.
هما من هاجماني
I can't help it.
ما باليد حيلة
Then let's hurry up and leave.
لنغادر هذا المكان بسرعة إذًا
Wait!
!انتظري
It's okay...
لا بأس
Robin...!
...روبين
Everything's... gonna be fine...!
ستكونين بخير
You're... still hiding something, aren't you?
لا تزالين تخفين شيئًا، أليس كذلك؟
That's okay.
لا بأس
But...
...ولكن لا يمكن للقرصان
cannot leave their crew...
...أن يغادر المجموعة
without their captain's...
!دون إذن قبطانه
So...
...لذلك
just...
...آمني
believe in Luffy.
!بلوفي
Wait, Robin!
!انتظري يا روبين-تشان
It's no use. Nico Robin will not break the agreement.
لا فائدة، لن تخرق نيكو روبين الاتفاق
How can you say that?
كيف تعرف هذا؟
Many years ago, an island was wiped off the map.
تدمّرت جزيرة معيّنة قبل سنوات عديدة
It was burned to the ground without a trace by a buster call...
حُرقت تلك الجزيرة على بكرة أبيها على يد نداء الدّمار
by order of the Marines.
الذي أصدرته البحريّة
The only survivor of that incident was a little girl named Nico Robin.
الناجية الوحيدة من هناك كانت الطفلة نيكو روبين
What?!
!ماذا؟
Five vice admirals and ten battleships...
خمسة من نواب الأميرالات وعشر سفن حربيّة
To that girl who witnessed such overwhelming military power,
بالنسبة لتلك الطفلة التي شهدت ،قوتهم العسكريّة الطاغية
the buster call is an inexpungible nightmare.
فإنّ نداء الدّمار كابوس لا يمكنها نسيانه
With that horror from her childhood now turned toward her friends...
إن كان الذعر المزروع في قلبها خلال فترة طفولتها موجه نحو أصدقائها
she no longer has the will to resist us.
فلن تملك الرغبة لمقاومتنا
Don't tell me...
...لا يمكن
you knew that all along...?
تقومون بكلّ هذا وأنتم تعرفون ذلك
Of course.
بالطبع
You monsters...
أيّها الأوغاد
Just how depraved are you monsters?!
!إلى أين سيصل انحطاطكم؟
Everything we do is for the sake of justice.
كلّ شيء من أجل العدالة
I deeply sympathize with that woman.
أتعاطف بشدّة مع تلك المرأة
Don't give me that crap!
!لا تعبث معي
You damn bastards!
!أيّها الأوغاد
This is the Enies Lobby Management Bureau.
هذا قسم الشؤون الإداريّة لإنيس لوبي
Is everything in order?
هل يسير كلّ شيء على خير؟
Yes, we're bringing the two criminals in right on schedule.
نعم، مهمة توصيل المجرمان تجري بسلاسة
The island is within sight, so we should be arriving shortly.
،بما أنّ يمكننا رؤية الجزيرة من أمامنا فسنصل قريبًا
Understood.
مفهوم
Well then, we'll be awaiting your return.
حسنًا إذًا، سنكون بانتظار عودتكم
After five years away, it truly feels nostalgic.
أشعر بالحنين، هذا طبيعي بعد خمس سنوات من الغياب
The nightless island, Enies Lobby.
جزيرة النهار الدائم، إنيس لوبي